So, this is the Hog, a model built with
trash and a giant 3D printed tire. As
always, this project began with a quick
sketch session where I put on paper a
general idea of what I want to build.
With the sketch finished, it was time to
start putting it together beginning with
the core of the machine made using
multiple pieces of different broken
electronics. Its cockpit was made using
a plastic party glass reinforced from
the inside to give the model a more
aerodynamic look.
Now, there was no easy way of obtaining
a tire in that size, so I had to make my
own. It was 3D modeled and printed in
two halves that were then glued together
making these beasts ready for the
painting process. For the colors, I
decided to go with shades of a purplish
kind of gray and a yellow accent color.
This machine lives in the mud, so I made
every piece super dirty and the model
was finished.